Let's work hard for another day!
This time on Haloste, I'm joined by Haruka Inoue from Morning Musume 24 and Hisaki Ebata from Juice Juice.
and Hisaki Ebata from Juice Juice.
These two are going to be our guests this time, so please stay with us until the end.
They are both in their third year of high school in Kyoto Prefecture, so it's quite unusual for two high school seniors to have so much in common.
At last month's Satoyama Umi event
The song of a local yurukyara of Uji Matcha City in Kyoto Prefecture
We sang a song together about a local yurukyara in Uji Matcha City, Kyoto Prefecture.
Do you have any episodes from that time?
I was very much impressed by the way you practiced the song together before the rehearsal and before the performance.
Yes, that's right. We sang together before rehearsals until just before the show,
Haruka Inoue was practicing for the spring tour at that time,
It was her first time to perform at Hina Fest.
Haruka Inoue had a lot to learn for the spring tour and her first Hina Fest.
Uncle Chacha of the Kingdom of Chacha
We managed to sing the song together.
I think it was a lot of fun.
Juice Juice will be releasing a new single on May 15.
Tokyo Blanc Nai Mono Love Aiko" will be released on May 15.
These three songs are.
Each song is refreshing, cute, or cool.
They have totally different impressions.
The sets and costumes are also completely different to match the songs.
I hope you can see many different JuiceJuice in this single release.
I think you can see various kinds of JuiceJuice in this single release.
I think you'll be able to see a lot of different JuiceJuice in this single release.
Morning Musume。24
JuiceJuice have started their spring tour.
This tour is a part of Morning Musume。
Morning Musume。 as Morning Musume。
We are going to perform many songs that we haven't performed in a while.
many of them.
songs will be sung under the new organization
I hope you will pay attention to them.
Yes, Juice Juice too.
This is the last tour for Mr. Uemura.
There will be a lot of corners that can only be done on the last leg of the tour, so I hope you'll be able to focus on them.
So I hope you'll be able to watch the show and concentrate on it.
Morning Musume。24JuiceJuice will be performing at the Nippon Budokan as well,
Both of them are going to practice hard for that.
Now, please take a look at this video.
Please take a look.
Akari Ruru Ruru Yumeria Iichiko Risaki Sakisaku Ru Akari
Meru
Dream
Ria
Ichiko
Risa
Risaku
Sakura
Akari
Mifu
We've been saying this for a long time.
We had been saying it for a long time.
So, I think we have done a lot of rehearsals,
I think we've done a lot of rehearsals, but today is the first day, in a good way, without thinking it's the first day,
This is the best part,
Let's have fun from the beginning so that we can make the limit.
And only one horizontal line.
I think there are people watching from above,
Let's be careful and let those who can only come today enjoy themselves.
We are Jujutsu!
Lusty, lusty, Dangerous
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I don't love you, I love you
Tokyo, tonight it's going to overflow
Lady on, tomorrow will come true...
What? You're working today, right?
Why are you doing this?
I can't get out the real Phong
I hate you more
The story of feelings When you get out
Sono Tsuki no Kanade de
Temptation Night Air Joy
Come on, change it up
The Handle That Takes Away Sleepless Love
Girlish Volley Maid Take away the steering wheel Sleepless Love on the Passenger Street
Let's go see a new morning with a new me
Una Junation Insect's Hair Gently Let the Wind Take You Away
Brand new love is in the way
I love you, but I don't love you, and when you're nice to me, it clouds my vision
I don't love you, I love you after all
My cute GPS is freezing
My cute GPS freezes my eyes
But I don't realize it
I'm so excited to see the time you gave it to me
I can't stop listening to your voice
The voice of temptation that won't go away
I can't shake the claws of peace
Breath that stops breathing
Comp tension, in profile
Love and Joy
I'm piling them on top of each other someday
The things we pass each other with kindness
Faded away
There's only so many ways to go under the sun
Become a bond
Let's take a song
Graduation
It wasn't you
That's all there is to it
I'm drunk on the beating heart that I can't help but push
I'm drunk on the rush of love
Shedding five stars
I'm going for the first star
You're in a temper tantrum, you're in a snowstorm, you're in a snowstorm, you're in a snowstorm
Come on, change it up, change it up
Rival and sleepless in love Step on the stage
Good-bye, my heart is no more, I can't go back
No more I'm out Beyond the tears, blotting Tokyo
This is Akari Uemura from JuiceJuice. So, the first day of JuiceJuice concert tour 2024 One Line has arrived!
This time, we called it "One Line", which means that the 11 of us are going to run together with our feelings in one line, but we really want to make a run for the future.
I'm really happy that MIFU came back and we are able to work together as a complete band.
I am also very happy that we are able to work as a complete unit and have a lot of fun.
I'm very happy that MIFU came back and we are able to work together as a complete unit and have a lot of fun.
When I was working on the engine for JuiceJuice's live this time
I was told by my teacher that I should always feel JuiceJuice.
I was pushed to do my best.
I felt like I had a gear up that I had never felt before.
I had an experience that I could only feel at this show.
I want to bring a fresh and exciting feeling to the people who come to JuiceJuice concerts this time.
I want to bring a really exciting and fresh feeling to those who come to the JuiceJuice concert this time. I hope that those who come to JuiceJuice's concerts this time will also enjoy this tour, which is filled with all the love that JuiceJuice has to offer,
I hope you will enjoy the tour as well. We hope you will enjoy the tour as well.
Spring tour has started! Yay!
Everyone's enthusiasm was so great that it was overwhelming and gave me a lot of energy.
I was a little nervous because it had been a while since I was on stage.
But all the members, fans, and staff were so warm and friendly.
I felt like it was like juice juice there.
The warmth of the stage was like juice juice, it was really like juice juice, the warmth was like juice juice.
I felt that the warmth of the show was really like juice juice, and it was really nice.
There are many more tours to come.
I hope you will cherish each and every one of them.
This is also Uemura-san's last tour.
I want to cherish the time with Mr. Uemura and the time with the 11 of us.
I hope we can make this tour even better. I will do my best!
With Haruka Inoue of Morning Musume 24,
Haruka Inoue from Morning Musume 24 and Kisaki Ebata from Chus Chus.
From here, we would like to talk a little about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so let's answer them in a quick tempo without thinking too much.
Yes. Ebata-san, whose trademark is a butt wipe, what do you recommend to use? I will ask you a few questions, so let's answer at a quick tempo without thinking too much, yes.
How do you recommend using the wipes?
As a pillow.
What do you want people to see in the music video for the new song?
Akari Endo's cool expression.
In one word, what kind of person would you describe Ebata Kisaki as?
She talks.
I'd say he talks.
Kisaki is a dexterous Mr. Yanagida.
What is your favorite recent creation?
A knitted card case.
What is the best moment to be a member of JuiceJuice?
The moment when we are all having a good time together.
Thank you very much.
The most surprising thing is
Using the wipes as a pillow.
I get a lot of surprises.
It's not like you take out one of the wipes.
They use the bag of wipes as it is.
on the bullet train, in the car, or on the road.
I put them on my head.
It's very useful because it suppresses vibrations and provides a stable cushion for sleeping.
If it were a pillow, I'm sure there are other things you could use, but why are you using a butt wipe as a pillow?
I have a little brother, and he was only 0 years old when I entered the Hallopro trainee program.
So I grew up with wipes in the house all the time.
I have been using wipes for about 5 years since I was a trainee.
One day I found the technique when I was in the Shinkansen well and I've been using them ever since.
I've been using them for a long time.
I carry the wipes with me every day.
I often get my hands dirty when I eat.
I often get my hands dirty when I eat, so if there are wipes with me, I can wipe them right away.
So I mainly use them to wipe my hands.
Also, if I were to describe Ebata Kisaki in one word, it would be the character for "talk.
That's right. I like to talk a lot,
Last month, we had a bus tour,
We had a bus tour last month, and during the bus ride, each member of iceJuice spoke by himself or herself.
During the bus ride, there was a part where each member talked by themselves.
While the other members were singing and playing games.
I talked all the way to and from the bus.
I really like talking that much.
I hope to talk a lot on the radio someday.
If you have any questions for Haruka, please ask her after the vtr.
me
juice juice news single tokyo brown may 15 onside me no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
So vague
juice juice news single nai nai mono love may 15 onside
Haloste
Next I would like to ask Haruka-chan some questions!
I'll do my best.
Haruka-chan will turn 18 in about 2 weeks
What would you like to do when you turn 18?
I want to wear mature clothes.
Haruka says that her motto is "calmness.
What is your favorite place or item to calm down these days?
I keep a key chain of my favorite character
I keep a key chain of my favorite character in my bag.
What are you personally interested in now?
Movies.
If you could have one wish come true, what would it be?
I wish to have 30 hours in a day.
It's been almost a year since you joined Morning Musume。
This past year
How would you describe the past year in one word? Strong winds.
Thank you very much for that last question.
I thought you have a very good sense of words, but what made you say "fear"?
First of all, it's because it's been a tough year.
Right after I joined the band, we had the fall tour and the 25th anniversary concert.
And then there was the 25th anniversary concert.
I had a lot to learn.
I guess I was afraid that if I didn't stand up properly, I'd get blown away.
I thought it was fear that if I didn't stand up properly, I would get blown away.
It's so great!
And then there's turning 18.
I'm going to be 18 in two weeks.
I'm going to turn 18 in a couple of weeks.
I'm really curious.
I want to wear mature clothes.
I always buy the same kind of clothes
I always buy the same kind of cute clothes.
When I turn 18, I'd like to try on mature clothes.
I'd like to try mature clothes when I turn 18.
That sounds good.
What exactly do you mean by mature clothes?
That's right.
Clothes that aren't frilly.
I often buy those kinds of clothes.
And I often wear skirts.
I'd like to start buying pants.
I see. I often wear pants, so I would like to buy pants.
I see. A while ago, I gave him some of my hand-me-downs,
But were they cool? Not mature clothes?
What kind of clothes did you give them?
I think they were mostly black.
So I think I contributed a little bit.
I'll continue after this.
This is Machiya Kimiyami.
I'm Rocco Doi from Otonoma.
I will work hard to complete the project.
What would you like to make this time?
This time, I'm going to make a poele of Madite scallops.
Brezezoe of Chinese cabbage
Let's enjoy cooking until the end!
I look forward to working with you!
It's a lot of fun!
Certainly a little stressful
Looks like it feels good
That was easy.
Now, let's see what we're going to do this time.
Now it's time to cook the fish.
We're going to start with the skin, but the skin tends to stick to the iron pan, doesn't it?
There's a way to make it float by using more oil, but it's a little bit different.
But it's definitely not the same.
It's okay to use medium heat.
Add a little oil.
Here's a near-biz point.
Make sure the skin of the fish does not warp.
The skin will get squeaky.
I just made a cut in the skin, so I think it should be fine.
But if you don't hold it down, it will warp right back up.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's already warping.
Did you see that? For a moment.
If you don't hold it down, it'll come right back up.
I'll put it in a little slower.
I can do it, I can do it.
And here we go again.
Put the butter in.
Pour it over the top.
There it is, doctor... what a trick.
It's an allosé.
What's "arosé"?
It's a kind of "foie gras".
But you pour oil and juice on it.
It's like taking a slow bath.
You cook the skin as long as you can.
When you turn it over, it's about 70% done.
I cook the skin 70% to 80%.
You can eat scallops as sashimi.
And the pies, you can eat them as sashimi today.
I put lemon juice in this butter and add salt.
There's also something called "burnt butter force".
It's good.
The browning is so beautiful.
Fish, if you use these tongs, the meat will fall apart.
I'll show you how it's done.
Wow! So beautiful!
Is it ready? Shall I turn it over?
Yes!
Scallops, you're perfect, you can stay here.
Scallops are amazing, really pretty eyes!
Oh, they look so good!
One more time, with a lot of energy.
A little bit, yes!
Oh, I got it!
Oh! Perfect!
Smells good.
Put it back in here.
There we go.
Here you go.
Perfect.
Okay, then.
Next, make the sauce
Sauce making
Yes, sir.
If you don't put enough oil in the sauce.
If you don't put enough oil, it will explode.
You can use puchi paper or something like that.
You don't want to take the flavor out of a fish that's just been grilled.
I don't want to take the flavor out of the fish.
I just want to keep the oil.
It'll pop.
50 cc.
I'm going to remove the alcohol.
It's alcohol, so it burns.
It'll catch fire.
I'll give it a try.
Will it light?
Will it start?
No?
No, it didn't.
It's already gone.
I'm burned.
Look at the color on this one.
That's the flavor.
I heard you're doing some kind of live show.
Yes, that's right.
This time, we're going on a 47 prefecture tour.
We're going all over the country.
So we're going to Saga Prefecture, my hometown.
Outside of Japan
I'm looking forward to it!
Everybody says "Ohayo" (good morning).
In my hometown, they call out the names of the members before the event starts.
So I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm happy to play in my hometown.
I'll be back the next day for another game with my family.
Hexagone
I'll taste it and if it's okay, we'll finish it.
The sauce will be ready in no time.
It'll be ready in no time.
Is it okay?
Yes, it's delicious.
We need to drain these vegetables once before serving.
I mean, drain them before serving.
It's cool like that.
Yes, it's a little bit curly.
It's cool to decorate it.
It's all about taste.
It's all about the presentation.
You make one.
Oh, I'll do that.
And one for Rocco.
I think it's a good idea.
Face-off. Pick a plate.
You go first.
You go ahead and pick a plate, Rocco.
I'm going to start with the noodles. They're blue.
I see. Royal blue.
Yes, royal blue.
Okay, let's see who's going to serve up what.
Let's start!
I'll do my best.
Sensei, you haven't put the sauce in yet, have you?
Sensei, I didn't put it in.
I left it all out.
I'm going to put the sauce first.
Yes, sir.
It's already in your head?
I don't know... but I've seen the way you put it on a plate before.
Oh.
I've never done that before.
Oh, that's great.
Let's give it a try.
Like this.
I see... that's what I'm interested in.
Oh, I see.
I'm curious about it.
It's like that, isn't it?
I'm under so much pressure.
Yes, yes, yes.
But how do you put it?
Let's put it this way.
It's okay. It's okay.
Here's your chance.
Oh, I see.
That's where we're gonna put it.
It'll be interesting to see if you decide...
Like this.
I see.
Now that we have a staff.
We'll all vote on it.
I'm nervous.
Let's vote on which one was better.
You look like a girl, Noroko.
You look like a girl.
I'm totally done with this.
It's finished, Sensei.
How confident are you?
I'm not so bad.
It's good.
Yes, it's good.
Okay, here we go.
Now, staff steam.
I'd like to put it to a vote.
Please wait a moment.
We have a winner.
Ready?
I'm ready.
We have a winner, Dudu. - Doodle doo! Wow! Yes! Thank you very much.
This is a professional who really went all out.
It looks so beautiful.
I still have to think about it once on my own, though.
You've done it many times.
He's a professional, so it's not very popular.
It's not very popular.
But Rocco, too...
He's so cute and gorgeous.
It turned out so beautifully.
It looks so delicious!
It's done!
Poirette of horse mackerel and Chinese cabbage is completedPoirette of horse mackerel and Chinese cabbage is completed
Brezee-aye of Chinese cabbage is ready!
How did you like it, Rocco?
I think I did a great job of arranging it!
It's so cute!
It was my first time to cook fish.
It was difficult, but it was fun!
It was the first time for me to cook fish, so it was difficult, but it was fun.
Then, please try it right away.
It was difficult, but it was fun.
It's delicious.
I ate a delicious looking rice cake.
Crunchy, huh?
It's so crunchy, and the sauce blends well with the fish.
If you had to give it a score, what would it be? To the camera.
I always say 65 when people ask me what my score is.
What? Is it always the same?
What about this one? Didn't you go over?
Sixty-five is a perfect score.
That's a perfect score.
That's because it's six.
I see.
Then you got a perfect score.
A perfect score.
It's so good!
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Please come visit Hello Kitchen again!
Please come again!
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
Looks like a very stylish and delicious meal!
Yes, it does.
I usually cook.
Lately I've been addicted to...
I'm into making egg soup.
Just adding egg soup to any dish for breakfast, lunch, or dinner is a great way to add color.
It adds a nice touch of color to any dish, breakfast, lunch or dinner.
I often make egg soup.
I often make egg soup, but I often add a little more sesame oil or something like that.
I put the eggs in thin and fluffy.
or the way I put the eggs in so that they become fluffy.
I've recently found my own special way to make it quick and easy.
I've learned to make it quick and easy.
If it's cooking, I'm addicted to egg soup.
Do you cook, Haruka?
Not really.
But I don't think it's really cooking.
I like making cream soda.
I mix syrup and soda water and put ice cream on top.
But I also want to cook.
I'd like to try making that ice cream from now on.
I like the ice cream. By the way, what kind of syrup do you put in it?
I often put shaved ice syrup that you can buy at the supermarket.
What flavor do you like?
Melon.
Melon is good.
I wish I could drink that soda you made someday.
A presentation of lyrics that touched my heart!
I think so.
Yay for the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart!
In this corner, you can listen to your own lyrics from the songs of Hello! Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics.
Project's songs and talk about their charms. Project songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Haruka Inoue, will be presenting.
Here are the lyrics I chose. The day I was able to stand on my head and the day I lost the game, in other words, all of them are proof that I lived my life single-mindedly.
I chose this lyric by JuiceJuice, This world is not abandoned.
Listening to these lyrics, I thought it was important to acknowledge myself even on the days when I had a good day or not so good day.
The tone of the song is very cheerful and uplifting, but the lyrics are also very inspiring.
The lyrics also cheered me up.
The lyrics also cheered me up and made me think that it is important to acknowledge myself on both good days and not-so-good days.
First of all, I really like the tone of the song,
The first verse is the one that sticks in my head the most,
I can easily remember the first verse, but the second verse doesn't always come to mind,
The second verse of this song is the one that left the biggest impression on me.
I like the title of this song a lot, and the idea that this world is not abandoned is one of my favorite lyrics.
It's a song that affirms me and makes me feel good about myself.
The new Venice Juice g sings very well, so the lyrics are easy to understand,
I'm here! I like this song very much,
It's my favorite song too,
I would like to listen to the second verse again.
I also think this song is very positive.
Both the lyrics and the tune.
I don't know how to say it at first.
There is a lyric that says, "Positivity is in full swing.
I really like that too,
I also like the way the lyrics say that the world is not so bad after all, as Kitagawa-san said,
The title of the song, the title of the song, it's like, how should I put it?
The title of the song, the title of the song, I really felt that it was the type of song that would cheer me up,
I really like JuiceJuice's songs and lyrics.
So we are the same.
It's good, isn't it?
Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。's songs are not often performed in full.
Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。's live performances are often one-half or one chorus, so I'm sure there must be some of you who like the full second verse.
I'm sure there are some of you who have favorite lyrics in the second full song, so I thought it would be good if we could pick up the full song again.
I thought of that when I looked at the lyrics of the second verse again.
I hope you all pay attention to the lyrics of the second verse and give it a listen!
Please look forward to seeing Haruka Inoue of Morning Musume。 24 and
Haruka Inoue from Morning Musume 24 and Kisaki Ebata from Juice Juice.
As I mentioned at the opening of the show
Morning Musume。24JuiceJuice have both started their spring tours!
For those of you who are watching Haloste, I'd like to share with you some of the things we've learned on this tour.
I would like to introduce what each of us is conscious of in this tour.
Let's go!
Let's do it!
I, Evata, wrote "posture".
I really like ballet-like beautiful movements of hands and feet.
I chose this word because I want to make beautiful movements with special attention to posture, shoulders and neck.
Yes, I chose to move.
On tour, there are many places where we have to move around in a narrow space because of the set.
I'm careful not to look like I'm flailing around.
We've just talked about what we both want to do.
By the way, do you have any essentials that you take with you on tour?
I want to concentrate before the show.
I want to concentrate before the show, so I'm bringing a Ramune so that I can take glucose.
It's sweet, so it's easy for my brain to work.
I'll bring headphones.
I'll bring some earphones or something that I can listen to music with.
I don't have any particular preference.
I'm not particular about earphones or anything that allows me to listen to music, but headphones block out the sound of the surroundings.
I wear earphones when I'm traveling, but
I wear earphones when I'm traveling, but use headphones when I'm backstage.
It's easy to concentrate, so I carry headphones with me.
Recently, I put a few grains of honey throat lozenges in a plastic bottle,
I carry a lot of throat lozenges,
I try to carry a lot of throat lozenges with me.
I often carry throat lozenges with me,
I often carry throat lozenges with me, but I have never put them in a plastic bottle and drank them,
I would like to try it next time.
I would recommend it because it quenches your thirst quite well.
We both carry sheepskins like this to moisten our throats and do our best. - I'm too clumsy for my own good.
I don't like to hate it.
Clumsy paradise that I can't get over with a smile
Someone who is serious
I can't relax anymore if there is
They say if you can just reach out with your hand
I'll notice you like you could smile
Everybody, everybody, everybody has the same scene at night
I can't say I'm sorry
You know, thrill, thrill, thrill, this conversation...
I can't believe we're doomed to meet on this moon.
I know there's no place, paradise
I'm alone and rough. I'm alone and great.
There's nothing like being able to watch your favorite movie.
I'm not gonna run away again.
I'm not running away again
No, I won't. I won't. I won't ever.
I'll never, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever
Praise me, praise me, praise me, praise me, Paradise
So much praise, so much praise, so much praise
Come on, praise, praise, praise Paradise I won't run away again
I'll never run away again
I won't run away again when I run away, I won't, I won't, I won't, I won't, I won't
It's so refreshing to the soul
Come on, praise me, praise me, praise me, praise me, praise me, praise me, praise me, praise me, praise me, praise me, praise me, praise me
I'll never, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever
Come on, praise me, praise me, praise me, praise me, praise me
I don't want to praise you, Paradise, look at me rather than the cherry blossoms
Haruka Inoue of Boning Musume 24 and
JuiceJuice's Kisaki Ebata presents Haloste.
It's time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
JuiceJuice is going to release
New single on May 15!
Tokyo Blur Naemono Love
Oaiko will be released on May 15!
All three songs are completely different
so please listen to them as many times as you like and enjoy them a lot!
I hope you will listen to them many times and enjoy them a lot.
I hope you enjoy them as much as I do.
And on May 15th, Morning Musume。 23 Concert Tour Autumn
Lever Ending Employee Award Special and
Lever Ending Employee Award Sanctuary
Mizuki Fukumura Graduation Special will be released!
This is the first tour I participated in, so I am really looking forward to seeing it!
Morning Musume。24コンサートツアー春
More Morning Musume。 is now underway!
This weekend they will be performing in Nagano and Niigata!
The final show will be held at Nippon Budokan on May 27.
Please come and visit us!
Juice Juice Concert Tour 2024 One Line is now underway!
This weekend we have a show in Osaka.
We are also going to have the final show at Nippon Budokan on June 14,
We hope that many of you will come to see us.
And Hello Project Hina Fest 2024!
Juice Juice, Beyones Premium, Tsubaki Factory, and Ochanoma Premium are now available on Hello Project Stream.
These will be available until May 6, so if you haven't seen them yet, please do so.
Morning Musume。24 will perform at Japan Jam with Anjelm and Beyons.
Morning Musume。24アンジュルム will perform on May 3 and Beyoncé will perform on May 4.
This will be my first Japan Jam, so I am really looking forward to it!
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
This time I'll be with Haruka Inoue from Morning Musume 24 and
and Kisaki Ebata of Juice Juice.
Good bye.
bye bye.